Guide to the Charles Seymour, President of Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Post-war planning board records, 1943-1945; Series III
  - New Jersey Commission on Post-War Economic Welfare: 1st Report, 1944 February 28 (Box 198, Folder 67)
  - Personnel Committee, undated (Box 198, Folder 68)
  - Policy and Program Committee, 1944 (Box 198, Folder 69)
  - "Post-War Connecticut" - interim report of the Board, 1944 (Box 198, Folder 70)
    - [typed copy], 1944 (Box 198, Folder 71)
    - Supplement to the interim report to the Board, 1944 (Box 198, Folder 72)
    - "Quick Facts" summary of the interim report of the Board, 1945 (Box 198, Folder 73)
  - Program of work, 1943 (Box 198, Folder 74)
  - Publicity, press releases, C.S.broadcast, etc., 1944 (Box 199, Folder 75)
  - Pulpwood Industry for Connecticut: Cromie, Pape, Rogers, 1944 (Box 199, Folder 76)
  - Report to the Governor, 1944-1945 (Box 199, Folder 77-78)
    See also: box 198, folder 70
  - Report to the Governor:, 1944, undated
    - Committee reports, 1944 (Box 199, Folder 79)
    - Miscellaneous materials, undated (Box 199, Folder 80)
    - Preliminary report, special report, 1944 (Box 199, Folder 81)
  - Resolution of the Board to the United States Congress, 1943-1944 (Box 199, Folder 82)
  - Resolutions re: budget, grants, legislation, 1944-1945 (Box 199, Folder 83)
  - Seymour, Charles
    See also: box 193, folder 6
  - Charles Seymour's Commission to the Board, 1943 July 28 (Box 199, Folder 84)
  - United States Department of Commerce, 1944 (Box 199, Folder 85)
  - Waterbury, Connecticut: City Plan Commission: Annual Report, 1944 (Box 199, Folder 86)
  - Waugh, Albert
    See: box 193, folder 7
  - Yale University: Institute of Human Relations, 1944 (Box 199, Folder 87)
- Council of Masters, minutes, 1937-1958; Series IV
  - Council of Masters: Minutes, 1937 October-1945 June (Box 200, Folder 1-6)
  - Council of Masters: Minutes, 1945 July-1950 June (Box 201, Folder 7-10)
- Addresses, speeches, and biographical clippings, 1937-1956; Series V
  - Addresses and Speeches, 1937-1943 (Box 202, Folder 1-6)
  - Addresses and Speeches, 1944-1947 (Box 203, Folder 7-11)
  - Addresses and Speeches, 1948-1950 (Box 204, Folder 12-15)
  - Addresses and Speeches: carbon copies, 1937-1950 (Box 204, Folder 16-17)
  - Addresses and Speeches: carbon copies, 1937-1950 (Box 205, Folder 18)
  - Addresses and Speeches: printed & mimeographed, 1937-1948 (Box 205, Folder 19-27)
  - Addresses and Speeches: printed & mimeographed, 1948-1950 (Box 206, Folder 28-29)
  - Addresses and Speeches: undated and fragmentary manuscripts, 1948-1950 (Box 206, Folder 30)
  - Newspaper clippings (photocopies), 1943-1956 (Box 206, Folder 31)
  - Clippings, 1937-1950s (Box 207, Folder 32-39)